<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonathan Choi</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jonathan Choi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/blog/my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Hey Guys! Welcome to my blog! I really like to watch movies, play basketball, go bowling, cook, and make music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Choi jjc4292 healthinsurance &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;healthinsurance.csv&amp;quot;) kaggle_income &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;kaggle_income.csv&amp;quot;) 0. Introduction I have chosen a dataset that contains data on healthcare insurance coverage rates before and after the Affordable Care Act, and the other dataset I have chosen is one that covers US household incomes across state, county, city, and more. More specifically, US household income contains 19 variables ranging from State code, State name, State abbreviation, county, city, zip code, longitude, latitude, mean household income, median household income, the number of households, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Choi jjc4292  Modeling  **0. I have chosen a data set that contains data on Medical Costs that are billed by insurance to patients. This data set contains 7 variables ranging from sex, age, bmi (body mass index), the number of children they have covered by insurance, whether or not they are a smoker, region, and medical charges from insurance. This data set looks at different factors that may contribute to predicting medical costs billed by their insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>